Like, so I just was like, what's about to happen?
So it was like the seas parted, the nice dude,
then this other dude, this other dude,
then this one little short, bald-headed nigga come up to me
and he's like, you need to get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, like the f-f-f-fut, like it's spit.
It's spit.
I said, what are you talking about?
Why do I need to get out of here?
Because we fucking said you need to get out of here.
These are the moments when you really are like,
why don't I know Taekwondo?
You know, because you're like, I could get arrested,
but I would have given them all.
Oh my God, are you okay?
Sorry.
But see, I would have given them that, you see?
You see?
I could have given them all of that.